capitalone.com 2000-11-10

# Capital One: Privacy

#### Privacy

At Capital One we understand that the protection of consumers' privacy is an important public concern. Accordingly, we have adopted this Privacy Statement to serve as the foundation for our internal privacy policies and procedures. It is our commitment to providing meaningful privacy protection for our customers.

  1. **Information Quality**  
We maintain procedures to assure that the personal information we collect is accurate, up-to-date and as complete as possible. If we obtain information about consumers who are not our current customers, we strive to treat this information in the same manner as we treat information about our existing customers.
  2. **Use Of Customer Information**  
We collect personal information from our customers themselves, from when we provide products or services to our customers, and from consumer reporting agencies and other outside sources. We use personal information only for purposes of administering our business activities, providing service, and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers.
  3. **Do Not Solicit Option**  
We recognize that some of our customers do not want to be solicited for offers and promotions from us. So, we provide our customers the option to have their names and addresses removed from our mail and/or telephone solicitation lists. We have procedures that assure a consumer's name, address, and telephone number are removed from our marketing lists.
  4. **Information Security**  
We maintain technical and organizational safeguards to protect the confidentiality of personal information about our customers against (i) unauthorized access or disclosure, and (ii) accidental loss, alteration, or destruction.
  5. **Maintaining Customer Privacy With Our Business Partners**  
We strive to ensure that the companies we use as our business partners support our commitment to privacy protection in their handling of personal data about our customers.
  6. **Employee Education**  
We provide training to our employees about their responsibilities under this Privacy Statement, and we expect them to do their parts in protecting our customers' privacy. We also conduct regular internal audits to support our commitment.
  7. **Privacy Statement Is Available to Customers**  
We want our customers to know about our commitment to providing privacy protection. Therefore, this Privacy Statement is available upon request to customers, shareholders, employees, governmental authorities, and members of the general public.

**Capital One Web Site Privacy**

**Types of Information**  
Anytime you visit our Web site, Capital One may collect and store information about your visit, such as the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com if you are connected from an America Online account), the date and time of your visit, the Internet address of the Web site you left to visit Capital One, the names of the pages you visit while at our Web site, and the Internet address of the Web site you then visit. If you are using our online services to access your account information or to complete financial transactions, information about these transactions may be collected and reviewed by Capital One-authorized individuals.

**Collection and Use**  
When you use various calculators, planners, or questionnaires on our Web site, you may be asked for personal information in order to complete the requested analysis or evaluation. This information may be retained and used by Capital One.

Electronic technologies assist Capital One in collecting information when you visit our Web site. The information gained through the use of such technologies may allow us to offer you the kinds of products and services you like and to determine that your visit is in accordance with our Web site Terms of Use.

For example, Capital One's Web site, like many others, uses "cookies." This small electronic file, which may be written to your hard drive when you visit our Web site, may be used to help Capital One understand what parts of our Web site visitors find most useful. If you choose, you can set up your Web browser to inform you when cookies are being set or you may choose not to accept cookies. A decision not to accept cookies could limit your access to some of the functionality and services that are available on our Web site.

**Online Applications**  
If you submit an online application, access your personal account information, or send Capital One an e-mail, Capital One may enter the information you send into its electronic database. You may also be contacted by Capital One for additional information. If Capital One uses a business partner to help it deliver the services to you, your personal information will be retained on either Capital One's system or its business partner's system in order to provide you with the services you have requested.

Most of the forms on our Web site encrypt the information you send across the Internet to Capital One and the information we send back to you. If a form requests confidential information, such as your account number, credit card number, or social security number, we will use encryption technology to protect your privacy. If you want to transmit information to Capital One outside the form, that transmission may not be encrypted and is not necessarily secure against interception. If your communication to Capital One outside the form is very sensitive or confidential, you may want to call Capital One or send that communication by regular mail rather than ordinary e-mail.
